dl-file.com 2018-05-29

# DL-file.com - Easy way to share your files

## Privacy Policy

* * *

Dl-file.com (we or us) is an online file storage provider. Your use of this service is controlled and ruled by this Privacy Policy.

The main goal of this Privacy Policy is to determine the privacy of Dl-file.com visitors. It involves the following: providing information about the Dl-file.com service and indicating the possible ways of how the personal information you provide might be used and how your personal information is secured on this website. The Privacy Policy might be renewed sometime in the future, so we ask you to check this document regularly to see the latest version.

Controlling Your Information Preferences

You are able to verify, edit, and renew your Personal Information while using settings in your Dl-file.com profile or account (if you have created one). You can also do that by e-mailing Dl-file.com team using our Contact Us form. Please, be sure to keep your password confidential and inviolable by not sharing it with anyone else.

**Information We Collect and How We Do It**

Personal Information

You can use particular features of Dl-file.com without sharing your Personal Information. Dl-file.com collects information that identifies you only if you decide to register with Dl-file.com and share your Personal Information with us. Such information includes your username and e-mail address. Dl-file.com is committed to not sharing, selling or renting your personal information to any non-related parties.

Usage Data

Dl-file.com automatically gathers data of its users. Such data involves the operating system you use, your Internet Service Provider, the Web browser, the and IP address as well as the links you use and the time and duration you spend using Dl-file.com. We collect Usage Data in order to understand how people use our services and to improve its quality. For instance, Dl-file.com uses the IP addresses to identify our users and manage the download limitations and visitor sessions.

Cookies and Web Beacons

Dl-file.com is not using tools in order to collect Personal Information. This applies to Cookies (text files allocated in your computer to identify your device and Web browser as you use the Service) and Web Beacons (electronic files, allocated in a website to monitor usage). ). We only use cookies and web beacons to indicate and evaluate our Users’ preferences and needs in order to increase the relevance and quality of our Service. We only use the encrypted number cookies that don’t contain any sensitive information. No other sources or companies are able to reach the information about our User that we store in our local database. Usually, Web browsers are configured to automatically accept cookies, but you can change that on your browser settings and choose either to not receive cookies at all or to be warned every time before accepting a cookie. Dl-file.com is not sharing any personal information about their users to other parties.

**How We Use and May Share Information**

In general, Dl-file.com uses Personal Information only when we need to communicate with our users about the Service we provide. This involves answering user requests, managing payments, announcing new products and services or simply communicating with users about the Service. Dl-file.com is obliged not to reveal its users’ Personal Information, except in the cases stated in the Privacy Policy.

Ad Networks

Dl-file.com might partner with third-party marketing and advertising businesses (“Ad Networks”). These companies might gather and use information about how our visitors use the Service in order to grant advertisements tailored for your interests. Such advertisements may be displayed through the Service itself or through other third-party websites. Ad Networks may locate or spot a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as Web Beacons to gather information regarding the use of the Service as well as other Internet websites or services.

Google Analytics

Dl-file.com uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. Google Analytics uses cookies in order to provide Dl-file.com with relevant information that helps us understand how our visitors use the Service. This allows us to improve our Service.

Data Retention

Dl-file.com will keep its users’ Personal Information until it is imperative for the essential activity. If you decide to cancel your registration and membership in Dl-file.com, your account will be deleted immediately together with all your Personal Information. From that moment on Dl-file.com will no longer use your Personal Information.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

Dl-file.com cooperates with the law enforcement officials, private parties, and the government to assure the compliance with the law. Dl-file.com might reveal users’ Personal Information or any other required information to other parties if it is required for any of the following reasons: to reply to legal requests (involving court orders and subpoenas), to secure the safety, property or rights of Dl-file.com, our members, or the third parties, to prohibit or stop any illegal and unethical activity, or to follow the law.

Sharing Your Information

We advise you to keep in mind that every time you share information in an uploaded file via Dl-file.com, that material might be obtained by the recipient. Therefore, anyone with the access to the shared material has the ability to upload, store or share your files as well as sending unrequested communications or redirecting payments. Dl-dile.com reserves the right to review User account content in order to check for violations of our Terms and Conditions. If we identify that your files violate the Terms and Conditions, we will ban your account and try to contact you. Dl-file.com reserves the right to cancel your account and remove your files.

**Security**

How Dl-file.com Secures your Information

Dl-file.com takes a lot of effort to secure the confidentiality of our users’ Personal Information. We apply appropriate physical and electronic measures to secure users’ information from illegal access. However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be ensured to be 100% secure. That means Dl-file.com cannot guarantee the complete security of information users upload and share using the Service. Consequently, the users upload and share files on their own risk.

Handling Content and Links to Other Websites

Users have the right to access, upload, and download their files and personal information at any time. They might also give access to their account files to other users by sharing their link lists or providing them with the download links. Dl-file.com is not the owner of your uploaded content and will only access your files for troubleshooting purposes. Users may determine the security setting for downloading their files.

The Service may also include links leading to other websites or allow other parties to send you such links. The use of the Service involving links to the material on Dl-file.com servers or websites that belong to the third-parties doesn’t necessarily mean that Dl-file.com endorse such websites or is related to it. Dl-dile.com doesn’t regulate the content that users upload or are sharing through the Service or the third-party sources. Users may access such content at their own risk and are advised to carefully read the privacy policy of such websites before providing them with any information.

Children’s Privacy Policy

Dl-file.com is not intended to consciously collect information from children under the age of 13. By using our Services, users have to assure us that they are at least 13 years old. If Dl-file.com is informed that the user is under 13-years old, we will have to terminate any account the user has on our system. Furthermore, if Dl-file.com is informed that we have accidently obtained Personal Information from a child under 13-years old, we will immediately eliminate it from our records.
